now we've got the full a start paying
into my guest star in its name instar
usually means optimal so and i built the
sapa summed giant tortoise plus hair
uh... combination and the question is is
the thing we've just built is even
optimal written universe authors with
optimal greedy was not we get out to
tell you what i would just a quick read
it's simple
let's execute a proficiency if anything
can go wrong
our friends our telecast back or call
zero four qazi roto kozyrev
so you cartel profs
are at the top that off
we get estay
an f_a_a_ has backward cross one for
kasich still cross seven
we have have
two g
which looks like it has backed word cost
by
or cut your
about five
so what comes off
after g comes off
we see a possible testing return it
autocross five
so the problem here is we actually got
the wrong answer out of a star
why didn't we keep traveling down the
after a packet was gonna turn out well
right going to be so cheap one plus
three widely stop
he stopped as this guy
the heuristic says like abandon all hope
you enter here
and we say okay you can stay on the
fringe now we're gonna go do something
else
as the problem is
this year i think it's nice to the
compassion towards the goal but it's
dangerous
because of it tells you this is really
bad news well you want to explore that
area of the graph
what went wrong here is the actual bad
goal costs here
was less than the estimated google costs
pain in particular
right this number six
overestimated the expense
and silly us we listen to the jurors
so we need or estimates right are
heuristic values they need to always be
less than the actual costs so if you
actually cost us three to get to the
goal
the heuristic a cancer zero a cancer
three but it better not say six organist
are being so often
so this is a key idea for getting a star
search to be correct stadium
admissibility
nothing to do with whether your it's
kind of your heuristics outlook on life
if you're outlook is
is bad if you have a heuristic which is
pessimistic would call that inadmissible
rhianna inadmissible heuristic is one
that always says your farther the golden
you are or maybe there's some good
happened so fast terrible company lian
right we thought that if
the heuristic lied to you and says that
something cost more than actually does
we can make mistakes
so here's a case where pessimistic
admissible heuristics they break off
malady
inadmissible or optimistic here s deck
uh... is one that always underestimates
the true cost
but hopefully not by too much
and me if you're a six conflict down
about traffic answer yeah the staff is
expensive i'm not sure how spent of not
more than this but it is going to be
pretty expensive and when it tells you
it's gonna cost at least eight you
believe it and you're safe and believing
it
inadmissible heuristic and slow down the
bad plans on the frantic and keep them
on the fringe for longer so you have to
explore what they lied to
but in the end
the heuristic never out leisure trip
costs
and that means the cheapest upload
benchley win until eventually to the
right thing
in napa heuristic h is admissible or
optimistic
if it's less than eight star an age
stars uh... defined to be the true
optimal cost you in your school
so of course we build here six h
there it will snippets of code to
execute the minke imputed to them
we don't know how to build each starve
and right but it's a mathematical thing
and so you would do if you would prove
the ph that you have built
is less than eight star which you can
tell
and then you know you're sick
so here's an example to admissible
heuristics very saw one
so on this kind of uh... pacman board
the manhattan distance change in expose
change in line
is admissible because if they're in a
while to get there that passed
but chances are the walls will make it
takes in due course
admissable on those left on the trip
costs it may be a lot less mature casa
pending on help tricky business
here's pancake flipping i said i have to
at least let in order to get if the
fourth and take about a position in or
get into this afternoon these two a flip
of size four
but i have to do a lot of other places
okay so here's a case where it's
admissible because a kind of to capital
one part of the solution
but there may be a lot self to the
solution that's going to cause you a
tinker cross as well
in practice
it's easy to define what admissibility
as
coming up with admissible heuristics
right which are lower bounds like this
but are still accurate enough to be
useful in search
is a big part of what's involved in
using a star in practice
the people already know this targeting
our camp up was a paper on the star over
them very easily
however
if you have a task that has an
interesting heuristic that takes a lot
of work to figure out how a star works
in my case because they start was not on
the specific
but your students